(Sheldon:)I'm nauseated
and feverish.
(Sheldon:)I believe I may have cholera.
(Leonard:)There's no cholera
in Pasadena.
(Leonard:)Just like last summer,
(Leonard:)when there
was no malaria
in Pasadena.
(Sheldon:)Well, if it's not cholera,
(Sheldon:)then based on a quick
Internet search,
(Sheldon:)the other explanations in
decreasing order of likelihood
(Sheldon:)are Hirschsprung's Disease,
botulism, a 30-foot tapeworm
(Sheldon:)or accidental ingestion
of chrysanthemum blossoms.
(Leonard:)When would you have accidentally
eaten chrysanthemum blossoms?
(Sheldon:)It's part of an
unlikely scenario
(Sheldon:)that involves sleepwalking
and a 24-hour flower mart
(Sheldon:)with a less-than-
vigilant proprietor.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Lord, my belly!
Ever had your
appendix out?
(Sheldon:)I haven't.
(Sheldon:)I've been meaning to,
but who has the time?
(Leonard:)Let's get you
to the hospital.
(Sheldon:)So this is how it ends...
(Sheldon:)with cruel irony.
(Sheldon:)Just as I make the commitment
to preserving my body,
(Sheldon:)I am betrayed by my appendix,
a vestigial organ.
(Sheldon:)Do you know